Guide to the Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Information File, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
- Box: 12, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: A Preliminary Survey of Wages and Personnel Practices in the Furniture Manufacturing Industry of the Los Angeles Area, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Author: Edward S. Feldman
- Box: 12, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Contracts of Employment, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Author: Co-Operative Union Ltd.
- Box: 12, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Union Contract Provisions, Eating and Drinking Places, 1961; Publication (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Author: California Division of Labor Statistice and Research
- Box: 12, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Il Divieto di Appalto di Mano D'Opera, 1962; Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Author: Italy Ministerio del Lavaro e Della Previdenza Sociale
  - Item 2: Il Contrato Collectivo di Lavoro, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Author: Dott. A. Guiffre
- Box: 12, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Provisions in Major Collective Agreements in Canadian Manufacturing Industries, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Author: Canada Department of Labor
  - Item 2: Forty-Two Provisions in Major Collective Agreements, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Box: 12, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: First Report of the Court of Inquiry into Certain Matters Concerning the Shipping Industry, 1966; Publication (Box 12, Folder 16)
    Author: Great Britain Court of Inquiry
- Box: 12, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Report of the Interim Commission to Study Collective Bargaining by Municipalities, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Author: State of Connecticut
- Box: 12, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Selected Provisions in Union-Management Agreements in New York State, 1963; Publication (Box 12, Folder 18)
    Author: New York Division of Research and Statistics
- Box: 12, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Collective Agreements, A Pilot Survey, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Collective Agreement Survey, Publication (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Box: 12, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Sample Contract for Local Units of Nurses in Hospitals and Nursing Homes, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Author: American Nurses' Association
- Box: 12, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Der Betriebskollektivvertrag in der Sowjetischen Besatsungszone, 1955; Publication (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Author: Alfred Leutwein
- Box: 12, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Convention Collective Nationale de Travail des Imprimeries de Labeur et Industries Graphiques, 1964, Publication (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Author: Journaux Officiels
- Box: 12, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: The Labor Contract Rejection Problem: How Account for it? What Are its Results?, 1970; Publication (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Author: Center for Information on America
    Notes: March 1970
- Box: 12, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Union Contract in Retail Trade: Food Stores, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 2: Union Contracts in Retail Trade: Men's Hat and Haberdashery Stores, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 3: Union Contracts in Retail Trade: Shoe Stores, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 4: Union Contracts in Retail Trade: Dry Goods Stores, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Item 5: Union Contracts in Retail Trade: Drug Stores, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Box: 12, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Collective Agreement in the USSR, Publication (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Author: Alexei Mukhanov
  - Item 2: The Collective Agreement in the USSR, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Author: V. S. Korotkov
  - Item 3: Directory of Membership and Services, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Author: Association of Consulting Management Engineers, Inc.
- Box: 12, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Disciplina del Rapporto di Agenzia e Rappresentanza Commerciale, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 26)
    Author: Ammiraglio Carocciolo
- Box: 12, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreements in New Jersey Educational Institutions, 1970; Publication (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Box: 12, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Industria Delle Calzature, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Box: 12, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Los Convenios Sindicales Colectives de Trabajo en el Campo Espanol, 1960; Publication (Box 12, Folder 29)
    Author: Organization Sindical Espanola
- Box: 12, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Gesamt-Arbeitsvertrag fur die Schweizerische Kartonagenindustrie, 1961; Publication (Box 12, Folder 30)
    Author: Ausgabe
- Box: 12, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Fibre Tessili Artificiali e Sintetiche, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Box: 12, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Tessitura Della Seta e Delle Fibre Artificiali, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Box: 12, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Provisions of Teamsters' Union Contracts in New York City, 1949; Publication (Box 12, Folder 33)
    Notes: July 1949
- Box: 12, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Autotrasporti Merci, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Box: 12, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Agreements: Expiration, Reopening, and Wage Adjustment Provisions of Major Agreements, 1954; Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Notes: October 1954
  - Item 2: Major Collective Bargaining Agreement Expirations, 1967, Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Clauses: Labor-Management Safety, Production, and Industry Stabilization Committees, 1956; Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
    Notes: December 1956
- Box: 12, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1945; Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: Contract Clauses for Cost-Conscious Employers, 1947; Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Author: Labor Relations Institute
  - Item 3: Wage Rate and Contract Provisions Report, 1947; Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Author: National Foremen's Institute
- Box: 12, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: The Economics of Collective Bargaining, 1950; Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Author: University of California
  - Item 2: Written Agreements in Collective Bargaining, 1938; Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Author: David J. Saposs
    Notes: April 1938
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining: How to Make it More Effective, 1947; Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Item 4: Extent of Collective Bargaining and Union Recognition, 1945, Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Author: U.S. Bureau of Labor Statistics
  - Item 5: The Challenge to Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Author: George W. Taylor
- Box: 12, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Your Stake in Collective Bargaining, 1945; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Author: T.R. Carskadon and S.T. Williamson
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Practice and Principle as Developed by Government Labor Boards, 1948; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Author: Harry Price Bell
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Author: Edgar L. Warren and Irving Bernstein
  - Item 4: Your Stake in Collective Bargaining, 1945; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Item 5: What Has Gone Wrong with Collective Bargaining, 1946; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Notes: January 20, 1946
  - Item 6: Workers and Bosses are Human, 1943; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Author: T.R. Carskadon
  - Item 7: Sound Collective Bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    Author: National Association of Broadcasters
    Notes: April 4, 1949
- Box: 12, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: An Appraisal of Collective Bargaining in a Free Society, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    Author: R. Conrad Cooper
    Notes: January 13, 1967
- Box: 12, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in Transition, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Author: The Ditchley Foundation
    Notes: November 1969
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Productivity, 1957; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Author: M.G. Levard & F. Archibugi
    Notes: June 19-22, 1957
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Reconsidered, 1971; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Author: E.H. Phelps Brown
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining in Transition, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Notes: November 1969, Copy 2
  - Item 5: Collective Bargaining Today as Seen at the National Labor Relations Board, 1965; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Author: Gerald A. Brown
    Notes: March 18, 1963
- Box: 12, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Seminario Internacional de "Las Vertientes" sobre la Negociacion Colectiva, Publication (Box 12, Folder 41)
    Author: Departamento Informaciones Sindicales
- Box: 12, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Summary: Aerospace Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
- Box: 12, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Reuther's Profit-Sharing Demand, 1958; Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Notes: May 1958
  - Item 2: Bargaining and Economic Growth, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Author: Henry Ford II
    Notes: June 22, 1964
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining in the Motor Vehicle and Motor Vehicle Equipment Industry, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Item 4: Sixteen Years of Progress through Free Collective Bargaining, 1964; Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    Author: General Motors
- Box: 12, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Report of the Court of Inquiry into a Dispute at Rootes Motors Limited, Linwood, Scotland, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
    Author: Great Britain Department of Employment and Productivity
- Box: 12, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Report into the Dispute Between the British Airline Pilots Association and the National Joint Council for Civil Air Transport, 1967; Publication (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Box: 12, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining: A Selected Basic Bibliography, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    Author: James L. Stern's
- Box: 12, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: A Critique of the Present System of Collective Bargaining and its Applicability to New Groups, 1970; Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Author: Shirly B. Goldenberg
  - Item 2: Some Proposals for a New Policy Toward Collective Bargaining, 1969; Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    Author: Aubrey E. Golden
- Box: 12, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 12, Folder 48)
    Author: Erwin Rausch
- Box: 13, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining for State and Local Governments; A Selected Bibliography of Recent Material in the State Library of Pennsylvania, 1971; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: State Library of Pennsylvania
    Notes: November 1971
  - Item 2: A Handbook on Collective Bargaining in the Public Service, With Special Reference to Michigan, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Author: Kalamazoo College
- Box: 13, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Recent Material on Collective Bargaining in Government, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Author: Princeton University
- Box: 13, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Meeting of February 12, 1969, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: Vermont Legislature
  - Item 2: The Legal Status of Public Employee Strikes and Collective Bargaining in West Virginia, 1970; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Author: David G. Williams and Don C. Hall
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining Rights of Swedish Civil Servants, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining Rights and Check-Off Dues of Public Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Notes: September 23, 1966
- Box: 13, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Resume of Collective Bargaining for Civil Servants in Canada, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Box: 13, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining for State and Local Employees; Three Papers, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Notes: December 9, 1966
- Box: 13, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Massachusetts Law Quarterly, 1967; Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Author: The Massachusetts Bar Association
  - Item 2: Report Relative to Collective Bargaining and Local Government Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Author: The Commonwealth of Massachusetts
    Notes: January 14, 1969
- Box: 13, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Requirements and Techniques for Municipal Employer-Employee Negotiations, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    Author: Michigan Municipal League
- Box: 13, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Final Report to the Governor and the Legislature, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Notes: January 9, 1968
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining and Civil Service in New Jersey: An Analysis of Civil Service Decisions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Author: Ernest Gross
- Box: 13, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Disclosure During Public Sector Negotiations: A Survey of Opinion and Practice, 1972; Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Author: New York State Public Employment Relations Board
  - Item 2: The Role of the Legislative Body, Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Author: Robert D. Helsby
- Box: 13, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining By Public Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Author: Glenn W. Miller
  - Item 2: Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Service: Answers to Questions About Executive Order 11491, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Item 3: Collective Bargaining in the Federal Sector, Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Box: 13, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Questions and Answers on Role of Assistant Secretary of Labor, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Item 2: Collective Bargaining Rights and Check-Off Dues of Public Employees, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Box: 13, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Papers on Bargaining Relationships and Practices, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 12)
    Author: League of Wisconsin Municipalities
    Notes: March 28-30, 1968
- Box: 13, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Summary: Bituminous Coal Industry, 1974, Publication (Box 13, Folder 13)
    Notes: August 1974
- Box: 13, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: 1948 Bituminous Coal Wage Conference, Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Notes: June 9, 1948
  - Item 2: Contract Negotiations in the Bituminous Coal Mining Industry, 1950; Publication (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Author: Harry M. Moses
    Notes: May 15, 1950
- Box: 13, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Management of Personnel Quarterly, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 15)
    Notes: Summer 1966
- Box: 13, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the Electrical Machinery, Equipment, and Supplies Industry, 1950-71, 1972; Publication (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Box: 13, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: The Collective Bargaining Relationship in the Hawaiian Electrical Industry, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Box: 13, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Les Conventions Collectives de Travail, 1950; Publication (Box 13, Folder 18)
    Author: La Documentation Economique et Syndicale
- Box: 13, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: The Case of the Missing Evidence, Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Author: Aims of Industry Ltd.
  - Item 2: Managers and Shop Stewards, Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Author: Arthur Marsh
  - Item 3: The Future of Voluntarism in Industrial Relations, 1966; Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Author: Allan Flanders
  - Item 4: Good Industrial Relations, 1972; Publication (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Box: 13, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Duration of Collective Bargaining Agreements in Hawaii, 1966, Publication (Box 13, Folder 20)
    Author: Helene R. Shimaoka and Joyce M. Najita
- Box: 13, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Statement for Joint Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1965; Publication (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Author: Jay Kramer
    Notes: November 17, 1965
  - Item 2: Notes on Labor Relations Law Relating to Hospitals, 1950; Publication (Box 13, Folder 21)
    Author: Milton R. Konvitz
    Notes: November 2, 1950
- Box: 13, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: A Study of Professional Librarians Being Conducted at UCLA, 1969; Publication (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Notes: June 19, 1969
  - Item 2: Review of Collective Bargaining Activities in Academic and Research Libraries, 1973; Publication (Box 13, Folder 22)
    Author: Association of Research Libraries
    Notes: June 1973
- Box: 13, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Fact Sheet on Collective Bargaining in the Longshore Industry, 1958-70, 1971; Publication (Box 13, Folder 23)
    Notes: Friday, September 10, 1971
- Box: 13, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Outlook For Collective Bargaining in New England in 1965, 1964; Publication (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Box: 13, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining Summary: Meat Products Industry, Publication (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Box: 13, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Collective Bargaining in the Maritime Industry, 1958-71, 1972; Publication (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Box: 13, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Where Will Industry-Wide Bargaining Lead Us?, 1950; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Author: Leo Teplow
    Notes: April 28, 1950
  - Item 2: Master Agreements in Collective Bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Item 3: Employers' Associations and Collective Bargaining, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Notes: May 1947
  - Item 4: Employers' Associations and Collective Bargaining, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Item 5: Employers' Associations and Collective Bargaining, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Notes: Part III, June 1947
  - Item 6: A New Force for Inflation, 1956; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Notes: May 1956
  - Item 7: Industry-Wide Collective Bargaining and the Public Interest, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Author: John V. Van Sickle
  - Item 8: Is Industry Wide Collective Bargaining Against the Public Interest?, 1945; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Notes: October 14, 1945
  - Item 9: Industry-Wide Bargaining, 1948; Publication (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Author: Leo Wolfman
- Box: 13, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Multi-Employer Bargaining, Publication (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Box: 13, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Organized Labor's Use of Coalition Bargaining: The Noose Gets Tighter, 1967; Publication (Box 13, Folder 29)
    Author: Lefkoe Consulting, Inc.
- Box: 13, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: An Experiment in Industrial Relations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 30)
    Author: Ronald Edwards
- Box: 13, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Municipal Collective Bargaining in Massachusetts, Publication (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Author: Joseph S. Hopkins
- Box: 13, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: A Guide to Municipal Collective Bargaining, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 32)
    Author: Connecticut Public Expenditure Council, Inc.
  - Item 2: Report of the Interim Commission to Study Collective Bargaining by Municipalities, 1965; Publication (Box 13, Folder 32)
- Box: 13, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Report on Collective Bargaining by Municipalities to Second Special Session of the One Hundred and Third Legislature, 1968; Publication (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Author: Legislative Research Committee
    Notes: January 1968
- Box: 13, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: The Conduct of Labor Relations Between the City of New York and its Employees, 1967; Publication (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Author: City of New York
    Notes: September 29, 1967
- Box: 13, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Municipal Collective Bargaining Agreements, 1970: Summary Report, 1971; Publication (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Item 2: Report of the Interim Commission to Study Collective Bargaining by Municipalities, 1965; Publication (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Box: 13, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: The Outlook for Collective Bargaining in New England in 1966, 1965; Publication (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Item 2: The Outlook for Collective Bargaining in New England in 1966, 1965; Publication (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Box: 13, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Labor Education Course Outline: Collective Bargaining, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 37)
- Box: 13, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Manual for Labor Disputes, 1946; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: Leonard J. Smith
  - Item 2: Management's Job at the Bargaining Table, 1948; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Item 3: An Outline of Management Strategy in Collective Bargaining, 1945; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: D.E. Buswell
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining, 1949; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: Herman Lazarus and Joseph P. Goldberg
  - Item 5: The Theory of Collective Bargaining, 1944; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: John W. Scoville
    Notes: August 8, 1944
  - Item 6: Management's Program for Making Collective Bargaining Work, 1946; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: Carroll E. French
    Notes: May 8, 1946
  - Item 7: Employer-Employee Relations, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: The Montreal Board of Trade
    Notes: January 24, 1947
  - Item 8: Collective Bargaining: How to Make it More Effective, 1947; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Item 9: Essentials of a Labor Contract, 1920; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: Edwin Gruhl
  - Item 10: Outline for Collective Bargaining: A Union Man's Check-List, 1949; Publication (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Author: Arnold F. Campo
    Notes: January 1949
- Box: 13, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Information for Employers and Unions Entering into a Collective Bargaining Relationship for the First Time, 1963; Publication (Box 13, Folder 39)
    Author: National Labor Relations Board
    Notes: April 18, 1963
  - Item 2: When Management Negotiates: A Guidebook for Sound Collective Bargaining, 1967; Publication (Box 13, Folder 39)
    Author: National Association of Manufacturers of the U.S.A.
- Box: 13, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 13, Folder 40)